== Official Website www.kissasia.co  ==
[Connecting to You]
Jiang Chaonan.
-Are you okay?
-How did you end up like this?
What happened?
Why am I only wearing my underwear?
No one wants to see that.
Do you remember how you passed out?
I had a few drinks,
and I wanted to make some instant noodles.
Then I saw the ceiling leaking,
so I wanted to...
grab a rag and wipe it up.
Then... I don't remember.
My head hurts.
Help me.
Can you get up?
Help him to the sofa.
Come on, be careful.
You freaked me out.
Mr. Jiang.
I checked your head,
and there are no obvious injuries.
I'll make a quick note for you.
"I'll Be Gone in the Dark,"
"Crimes of the Future,"
"Abnormal Psychology"...
You like reading these?
I know what you're thinking.
Studying criminal psychology
doesn't mean I'll commit a crime.
And "abnormal" doesn't mean
"perverted."
I didn't say anything.
Why are you so nervous?
Good thing he's fine.
We should be able to get off work on time.
Don't jinx it.
[Thread 3]
[Illusion of Transparency:
How can I see through you?]
Senior.
If you're skipping class
just to cause a fire or get yourself hurt,
I think you'd better go back to school.
I'm so lucky.
I keep falling but never get hurt.
The Eight Lords must be protecting me.
Stop bothering the Eight Lords.
Oh, right.
Why did that police officer
come back with you?
Officer,
what's wrong?
Did my kid disturb the neighbors again?
No, we just came by to check on you.
Do you mind if we go in?
No. Come in.
Alright.
Is he okay?
He has autism,
so he can be quite emotional.
He was being picky with his food,
so I gave him a lecture,
and he lost control.
Hao, that's enough.
Sir, you should comfort him first.
Hao.
It's okay.
It's alright. Hey...
It's alright. It's alright.
You're fine, okay?
The officer said it's fine.
Don't be nervous. Stop crying, okay?
Hao...
Sorry for disturbing the neighbors
and causing you trouble.
He'll calm down soon.
Is there anything else you want to know?
Nothing, but the neighbors
might still complain.
You need to be more careful.
Got it.
Thanks for your time. We're leaving.
Thanks.
Officers, what brings you here?
Are you here for Wen on the second floor?
Yes.
Ma'am, do you know him?
Yes, he's a divorced single dad.
He's a nice guy, and he's good to his son.
So, that little boy often cries like this,
right?
Yes, he often cries
in the middle of the night.
Not just that, he also smashes things.
Okay, got it. Thanks, ma'am.
-You're welcome.
-Watch your steps.
Your student ID.
[Lin Jiakai]
Thanks.
Oh, and this.
That police officer left it for you.
Why give me this?
What did he say?
It's for the scrapes you got when you fell
and rolled around on the ground that day.
Need help?
No, just a scratch.
I'll just apply the ointment
and put on a band-aid.
Thanks.
It's nothing.
You're still here.
[Psychology Department Lab]
I'm almost done.
Ms. Peggy, could you take a look?
Did I fill everything out correctly?
Just finish it up. I trust you.
Ms. Peggy.
Do you believe
I can see the connections between people?
I do.
Why? You have no way
to verify what I see, do you?
Believing is a relative concept,
not an absolute conviction.
[Psychology Department Lab]
Buddhism says
there are 4,500 instants in a minute,
and 405,000 thoughts could arise.
How can you tell
if someone had a moment of doubt
even when they believed you?
Ms. Peggy, I don't think I understand.
It means...
if you keep asking,
I'll get up and punch you.
At least tell me
what color the thread
above that nurse's head is,
so I know if I should pursue her or not.
Don't ask me every time
you see a cute girl, okay?
Are you sure you won't be upset
if I tell you?
I promise I won't be upset.
Honestly, there's no thread
between you two at all.
She probably doesn't even want...
I don't want to hear it.
Hey.
Hey. Hey!
My uncle texted me,
saying we have to
handle the leak ourselves.
He said it's normal
for an old house to have leak issues,
but this is too serious.
He said he'll come by this afternoon.
Let's stop by the breakfast shop later.
I want to buy an egg burger. I'm starving.
Me too, and a medium iced black tea.
Your treat.
Why should I treat you?
I wonder who ruined
my limited-edition instant noodles.
Why is that child crying so hard?
An auntie nearby told me
that he has autism.
Hey, where are you going?
Wait for me here. I'll be back soon.
Hey, Lin Jiakai!
I'm starving!
Hello, sir.
What's wrong?
Did someone report again?
We received a report,
so we're here to check on you.
This officer came last time.
He knows our situation.
But this is a report,
so we have to deal with it.
Can we go in?
Please.
Come in.
Come on.
Little one, are you okay?
What happened?
-You can tell me anything.
-Hao.
It's okay now, alright?
I can help with your homework.
Be brave.
Don't care about what your teachers
and classmates say, okay?
Kid,
did anything happen to you?
Is this enough?
Sorry for the trouble.
Perverted College Student,
why are you here?
Are you here for the crying kid upstairs?
Yes.
Hey, sir.
Sir!
Who are you?
-Hao!
-Hey!
Don't run.
What happened?
Hao!
Y-You beat that boy!
What are you talking about?
Excuse me, I need to look for my son.
You hit him!
Who are you?
That's right.
Why did you suddenly run over here?
Okay, forget it.
Dawei, let's find him first.
I know where to find him.
You better know where he is. Hao!
Dawei, Dawei!
Are you spacing out? Hurry up!
Yeah, let's follow him, hurry.
Hao!
Dawei, follow him!
Where are you going?
I'm looking for Hao!
How do you know where he is?
I just know.
Little one.
You're Hao, right?
You don't want to go home
because of your dad, right?
Okay, it's fine. We can stay here for now.
Can you show me your hand?
No bruises?
How's that possible?
Can I check your body?
I'll make a call.
Little one.
Hey,
I'll take you back
to put on some medicine, okay?
No.
I won't take you home.
We'll go to the hospital and see a doctor.
Don't worry.
We found Hao in the park nearby.
There really are bruises on his body
from being beaten.
Take his dad
back to the station.
Let's go to the hospital.
Okay.
This officer will take you to the hospital.
Can you get up?
Watch your head.
What's wrong?
Let's go.
Just follow him.
Why are you still here?
Aren't you done with your statement?
I just wanted to know
how the questioning with his dad went.
Did he admit to the abuse?
Yes.
He said he couldn't stand
Hao's emotional reactions
caused by his autism,
so he lost control and beat him.
But we didn't find
any medical records of his autism.
We'll arrange
a new medical assessment for Hao
to find out whether he actually has autism
or if his abnormal social responses
are caused by the abuse.
No matter how much
his dad says he regrets it,
or how much Hao wants to see his dad,
I think...
it's best that they live separately
from now on.
Why?
Because when I saw them
walking on the street together,
I saw the blue thread.
So, I thought
that maybe his dad
wasn't really good to him.
He was just pretending it
in front of the neighbors.
But the saddest part is...
even though his dad treats him like this,
he doesn't hate his dad.
Okay, got it.
I know you don't believe this, right?
I'll let you know if there's any progress.
Just go back and rest.
[Qishi Police Station]
What's this?
That college student left it
and asked us to give it to Hao.
He said if anything happens,
Hao can call him.
He lives nearby and can help.
I thought he was just some
immature college kid.
Turns out he's so kind.
Did the water pipe burst?
Why is it leaking so much?
How would I know?
I just called my uncle.
He said this place is ruined
and has to be restored.
He told us to move somewhere else
for two months.
He wants to completely renovate it.
Move somewhere else?
Where are we supposed to go?
No idea.
Maybe go to a relative's place
in Taipei, or...
You don't have any relatives
in Taipei, right?
No.
Maybe you can apply for
a temporary dorm or something.
It's too late to apply for it.
And I don't want to live too far away.
It'd be too inconvenient
for my part-time job.
Poor you.
Who is this?
Chief?
Why are they so expensive?
[Peipei Rental]
[One-Bedroom Unit with Balcony]
It's you.
What would you like today?
Three iced lattes to go.
Three iced lattes.
Anything else?
That's all.
210 TWD in total.
That's 300 TWD.
Here's 90 TWD change.
How did you get this?
Do you also hit on little boys now?
No.
I told your colleagues my intentions.
I know. Don't be so nervous.
As for Hao,
we've officially reported it
to the social welfare agency.
Don't worry.
Are you looking for an apartment?
Yes.
My landlord is taking it back
for renovations,
so I need a place to stay for two months.
But short-term rentals are so expensive.
I asked a few friends,
but none of them can help.
Actually, Jiang Chaonan
has been asking around for you.
You only need to stay
for two months, right?
Yes.
The landlord said
we can move back sooner
if the renovations are done early.
Well, I have a room
that the landlord uses for storage.
With a little cleaning,
it could work as a bedroom.
If it's only for two months,
you can stay there.
[Peggy Talks Love Psychology]
Everyone's online.
This is Two-Minute Love Live Stream.
[Two-Minute Love Live Stream]
It's fleeting, so don't miss it.
I'm Ms. Peggy.
Today,
I'm going to talk about
the illusion of transparency.
Illusion of transparency.
This is
a cognitive bias.
[Cognitive Bias]
We often overestimate
our understanding
of other people's
mental states
or
other people's understanding
of our mental states.
Like right now.
This is a question from Student A.
Student A said,
"My boyfriend would rather play games
than have dinner with me.
I was so mad
and ignored him for three days.
And he actually said he didn't know
what I was angry about."
Well,
this is what we call
the illusion of transparency.
You were very angry,
but you didn't explain it clearly.
So, he had no idea
what you were angry about,
right?
Even if
you've been
together
for a long time,
it doesn't mean
you'll be so connected
that you can even
read each other's minds, okay?
When there's a problem,
you need to talk it out.
In a relationship,
you must
communicate with each other.
[Communicate with Each Other]
That's how it lasts,
okay?
And stop messaging me
over and over.
One message is enough.
Thanks.
Love you.